Guide to the A Gathering of the Tribes Records MSS.198
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Audiovisual Recordings, 1983-2011; 13 Linear Feet in 9 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, 1 unknown profile containers, and 4 items in a shared cassette box.; 18.99 Gigabytes in 11 computer files; 305 items on audio and video carriers.
  - Subseries I.A. Video, 1983-2011
    - Swedish Film Week, New York, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0233, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0233)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 90 min.
    - Teach Tolerance, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 00:22:00; Original Format: VHS; Label: "Office Copy, Southern Poverty Law Center" (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0298)
    - Tribes Highlites, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 02:00:00 (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0041, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0041)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 112 min.
    - Tribes Highlites, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotations: "Tribes' Steve Cannon"; "Video - By Nick Cirabisi"; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0060)
    - Tribes Productions / Alice Zinnes, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0164)
    - Tribes Production / Amy & Friends, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0240, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0240)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 73 min.
    - [Unknown], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 52, Cassette ID: 198.0290)
    - Unusable, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0275)
    - VID #1, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0277, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0277)
    - Video Void #8, Studio [S_re], circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0181, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0181)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 31 min.
    - Voo / Doo Movies, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0001, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0001)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 116 min.
      Content was recorded from television. All commercial news programs.
    - "Watch Me", circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0054, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0054)
    - Personal Problems - Ishmael Reed, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements; Label annotation: "Reels 1 & 2 - 2-track audio". (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0270, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0270)
    - Planet Caravan, Episode 1, 2, 3, 7, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0191, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0191)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 111 min.
    - Planet Caravan, Episode 3, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0061)
    - Tribes Gallery, Music Added, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0153, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0153)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 26 min.
    - Two Iranian Poets, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0124, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0124)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 62 min.
    - Works on Paper: Star Black, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0009)
    - Lee Liu & Tong, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Promotional release (Hot Shots, Cool Cuts).; Label information: "attn. Diane Paragis; MCI; Reel #1; Autumn Ftg.; Lightning Ftg."; Original Format: 3/4 in. Umatic. (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0232)
    - Mona Lisa, 1985; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Commercial Release (HBO Cannon Video).; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0118)
    - Ishmael Reed: Savage Wilds, circa 1985-2007; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 00:30:00 (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0004)
      Original Format: VHS, Preservation note: This tape could not be digitized due to extensive tape damage.
    - Ishmael Reed: Hollywood's War on Ethnic America, Part 1 of 2, January 8 1987; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "Copy". (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0187)
      Original Format: VHS, Preservation note: "Recorded from television; Alan Keyes on C-SPAN and other programs"
    - Ishmael Reed: Hollywood's War on Ethnic America, Part 2 of 2, January 8 1987; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0314)
      Original Format: VHS, Preservation Note: This is an off-air recording of a televised program. It was not selected for digitization.
    - Ishmael Reed 6/25/90 Mosaic Books / 8316 - Patient - JF - 6-30-90 DG., June 1990; 1 media elements (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0188, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0188)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 107 min.
    - Smokin' Word '90, 1990; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 00:40:00 (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0021, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0021)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 42 min.
    - The House of Johnson - The Living Theatre, October 27 1991; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0175, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0175)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 100 min.
    - Last Crack: Burning Time, March 7 1991; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:17:00; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0034)
    - Poetry Reading, Prof. Cannon, April 17 1991; 1 media elements (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0184, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0184)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 49 min.
    - The Set Up, by Steve Cannon, Nuyorican Poets' Cafe - Music Added, May 13 & 29 1992; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0095, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0095)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 97 min.
    - The Set Up, May 1992; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotations: "5-13-92 - No Music. 5-29-92 - Music Added. No sucrose 'Steve Flubs' for Chump Intro." (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0028, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0028)
    - Chump Change, October 3 1992; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label Annotations: "By Steve Cannon, At Dixon Place" (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0043, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0043)
    - No Sucrose Intro / Chump Change, October 31 1992; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0120, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0120)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 58 min., Preservation Note: Previously recorded content appears between edits.
      Item 198.0141 contains an unedited version of "Chump Change."
    - Nuyorican - 1st Poet's Choir / Slam, December 18 1992; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0045, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0045)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 108 min.
    - The Set Up, circa 1992; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0157, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0157)
    - Steve Cannon: The Set Up / Chump Change / En Vogue, circa 1992; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0141, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0141)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 113 min.
      Item 198.0120 contains an edited version of "Chump Change."
    - Too Short - I Want to be Free, circa 1992; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:04:23; Promotional Release (Jive Records, Silvertone Records).; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0052)
    - Poets' Choir / 1st Night, 1992-1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label Annotations: "Whitney 12-31-92, Public 1-1-93" (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0040, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0040)
    - En Vogue, Whitney 11-10-92, Skep 11-17 / Tribes Interview 10-21-93, November 10 & 17 1992, October 21 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0090, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0090)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 101 min.
    - Butch Morris - Poet's Choir: Nuyorican 12-18-92, Whitney 12-31-92, Public Theatre 1-1-93, Nuyorican 2-11-93, Fez 3-9-93, 1992-1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0143, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0143)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 180 min.
    - Tribes at St. Mark's Church, January 29 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0056, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0056)
    - Poet's Choir at the Fez, March 9 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0100, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0100)
    - Tribes at the Fez, April 11 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0160, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0160)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 117 min.
    - MCI Q3 SED Japanese / MCI Q3 SED Chinese/Mandarin / MCI Q3 SED Chinese/Cantonese, July 7 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 00:01:30; Original Format: 3/4 in. Umatic; Spine label: "Client: MCI; Tape Location: Black Hallway A; Tape Number: A10; Title: Q3 SED" (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0306)
    - Now What, What Now? Rehearsal, Show, August 18 & 20 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "Steve Cannon, Butch Morris, Nick Video"; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0081)
    - Now What, What Now? Rehearsal, Show, August 18 & 20, 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0156, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0156)
    - What Now, Now What, University Sts. / Tribes, Ham Fish Library, August 20 1993, April 8 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0055, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0055)
    - It's About Time: John Farris, September 12 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0010, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0010)
    - Nothing to Lose, October 21 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0035, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0035)
    - Tribes Meetings, December 7 & 21 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0069, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0069)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 119 min.
    - What Now, Now What - Tilden Gallery, December 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0080)
    - What Now, Now What, December 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotations: "What Now, Now What 12-17-93, 12-31-93" (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0036, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0036)
    - Longshot BK Party / What Now, Now What at Bobs / Tribes Discussion, circa 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotations similar in appearance to those on cassette 198.0075, which is dated 1993. (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0076, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0076)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 121 min.
    - Lee Liu & Tong: "Asian-American Heritage Month", April 22 1994; 1 media elements; Label: "Hi-8 Bump-Ups with Address Track"; "Hi-8 Burn-In T.C."; "Reel #2 Part 2"; "Studio Shoot / BMCC" (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0305, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0305)
      Original Format: 3/4 in. Umatic, Duration: 15 min.
    - Now What, What Now, April 1994; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "Tom's Copy" (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0079, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0079)
    - Now What, What Now? by Steve Cannon, April 21 1994; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0204, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0204)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 5 min.
    - Now What What Now? - Context, April 21 1994; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "by Steve Cannon (c) 1994"; "cued for five minutes" (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0159, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0159)
    - Top of the World - Context, June 1994; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0144, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0144)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 67 min.
    - Tribes, Fish Library 10-15-94 / Gallery "Woodstock", 1994; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0068, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0068)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 80 min.
    - Willem de Kooning: Artist, 1994; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Commercial release (Mystic Fire Video, Inc.). (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0024)
    - Dora's Birthday / Kim's Caven, 1994; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0099, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0099)
    - Democracies in Chinatown: 1974-1994, circa 1994; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0014)
    - Cayenne: at Pyramid 1-22-94, Book Party 4-3-95, 1994-1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0101, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0101)
    - Top of the World - Nuyorican, March 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 01:05:00; Label annotation: "by Steve Cannon"; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0121)
    - Top of the World - Nuyorican, March 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 01:05:00; Label annotation: "by Steve Cannon"; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0093)
    - Top of the World - Nuyorican, March 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0139)
    - Top of the World - Nuyorican, March 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 01:06:00; Label annotation: "by Steve Cannon"; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0140)
    - Channel Zero: Planet Street, May 1995; 2 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 03:00:00; Commercial Release.; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0065)
      Currently no access copies are available.
    - Tribes Benefit, August 23 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Cassette sleeve annotation: "Xcluding The New Family & The Beaver's [Tail]" (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0113, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0113)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 35 min.
    - I. Reed, T. Reed, & V.H. Cruz: Tribes Benefit, November 17 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0255)
    - I. Reed, T. Reed, & V.H. Cruz: Tribes Benefit, November 17 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0254)
    - Victor Hernandez Cruz vs. A Gathering of the Tribes, December 2 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0077, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0077)
    - Poet's Choir, Context, 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0097, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0097)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 62 min., Preservation Note: Tracking issue due to source tape damage.
    - Gringo in Mananaland: A Musical, circa 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 01:01:16 Insert in cassette case with synopsis and quotations; Directed by Dee Dee Halleck.; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0147)
    - P-Town - 96 / Jan 7th - Tribes Knitting Factory, circa January 1996; 1 media elements (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0219, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0219)
    - Tribes - Nuyorican Poet's Cafe Part II, February 21 1996; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0074, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0074)
    - Carlos at IBM Garden / Biblio-Poets, April 4 & 6, 1996; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "Carlos - 30 min." (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0058, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0058)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 99 min.
    - Tribes Art Opening, April 1996; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0173, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0173)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 7 min.
    - Steve's Place - Hal's "Mother Said" Party / Star's "Waterworn", June 2 1996; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 02:30:00; Label annotation: "by S.L. Fung" (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0071, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0071)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 173 min.
    - Panel at Nuyorican Poets Cafe, July 14 1996; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0044, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0044)
    - Pat Winter's "The Buzzing of Insects" at Nuyorican Poet's Cafe - 7/14/96 / Butch Morris' Poet's Chorus at Metro Pictures in Soho Arts Festival - 9/8/96 / Charlie Parker's Night - 8/28/96, July - September 1996; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0046, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0046)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 124 min.
      Audio missing in some sections.
    - Film of Two Parties: Halloween '96 & Backyard, 1996; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0151, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0151)
    - Knitting Factory: Sabir Mateen, Butch Morris, Jason Hwang, 1996; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotations: "Sabir Mateen 6/24/96, Butch Morris - Band 7/8/96, Jason Hwang - Alternit" (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0032, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0032)
    - Small Gems. Close to Closing., January 10 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0098, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0098)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 17 min.
    - Tribes at Gershwin Hotel, January 18 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0030, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0030)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 87 min.
    - Tribes Reading - Barnes and Noble, January 29 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "Cam. Vipin" (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0087, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0087)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 46 min.
    - Star Black, Tribes Gallery, March 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0057, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0057)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 15 min.
    - Tribes Benefit, April 25 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "Video - Dor Green". (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0027, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0027)
    - Sarah Jones @ Gershwin Hotel with Edwin Torres; Beau Sia; Kris Lew; Bob Holman; Everton Sylvester; Carman B. Brown & Hilcato with Musicians, May 18 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0085, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0085)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 93 min.
    - Silhouette @ Isart Gallery, Montreal; Featuring Designer Daniel Mistiva, July 10 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0176, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0176)
      Two postcard invitations removed from cassette sleeve and moved to Series III. They can be found in Box 17, Folder 29.
    - Juma Santos - World Peace Drummers @ Gershwin Hotel 5/25/97 / Tribes Gallery Show - Jim Carl, 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 01:20:00; Label annotation: by Susan L. Yung. (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0114, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0114)
    - Suheir Hammad & John Farris 10/5/97 / Pedro Pietr1 10/12/97 at Ave B Social Club / Lorenzo Pace's "Triumph of the Human Spirit" 10/16/97 at African Burial Ground Breaking Ceremony with Giuliani, October 5, 12 & 16 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0086, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0086)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 122 min.
    - Eileen Weisman's "Off the Wall" / Remember These Nights... Ken McManus, Clara Sala, Letta Neely and David Morreale, at the Gershwin Hotel, 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0148, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0148)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 180 min., Preservation Note: Picture quality is very poor due to generation loss (a copy of a copy).
    - Zero Point Zero Tape 1, April 25 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0163, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0163)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 115 min.
    - Zero Point Zero Tape 2, April 25 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0109, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0109)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 33 min.
    - The Charlie Parker Tribute, August 25 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0073, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0073)
    - Sheila's Birthday Party 9/26/98 / Anthony Murell's Tribes Opening, circa September 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0135, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0135)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 58 min.
    - Gathering of the Tribes Poetry Reading, October 2 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Handwritten container annotation: "Exit Art #8". (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0008, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0008)
    - Skyscrapers, Taxis & Tampax, November 15 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0170, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0170)
    - Tribes: Exit Art NYU with Ishmael Reed / David Henderson Neo-Calif / Anthony Murrell 20 Class A Tobacco Suits / Elisabeth Atnafu East Village Universe, October - December 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0158, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0158)
    - Kokoro no tabi - Shuntaro Tanikawa, 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "'98.5.2" (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0066, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0066)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 54 min.
    - Tom Dent / A Reading Tribute, 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0122, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0122)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 192 min., Preservation Note: Recorded in low light; difficult to see.
    - "A Gathering of the Tribes" - The Public Theater, February 21 1999; 1 media elements (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0217, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0217)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 84 min.
    - Joe's Place, February 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0031, Box Digitized Access Files, File fales_mss198_0031)
      Original Format: VHS, Duration: 83 min.